Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XCII is arranged in 12 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XCIII is arranged in 2 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XCII. 1939 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 462-0. 1939 Convention. General
    - General, 1936-1939 (Box 601a, Folder 54)
    - Report of the Committee on Legislation., 1939 (Box 601a, Folder 55)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1939 (Box 601a, Folder 56)
      1939 May 8
    - Grand President's Worksheets, 1939 (Box 601a, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 462-1. 1939 Convention. Grand President's Convention Report
    - General, 1935-1940 (Box 601a, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 462-2. 1939 Convention. Constitution.
    - Recommendations for Brotherhood Constitution and Laws, 1936-1939 (Box 601a, Folder 59)
    - Text of Revised Constitution., 1939 (Box 601a, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 462-3. 1939 Convention. Hotel
    - 462-3. 1939 Convention. Hotel, 1938-1939 (Box 601a, Folder 61)
    - General, 1936 (Box 601a, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 462-4. 1939 Convention. Non-Delegate Appointments
    - General, 1937-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 462-5. 1939 Convention. Arrangements
    - General, 1938-1939 (Box 601a, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 462-6. 1939 Convention. Convention City for 1943
    - General, 1939 (Box 601b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 462-7. 1939 Convention. Delegates and Alternates
    - General, 1939 (Box 601b, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 462-8. 1939 Convention. Resolutions
    - General, 1939 (Box 601b, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 462-9. 1939 Convention. Committee on Rules, Order of Business and Ritual
    - General, 1939 (Box 601b, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 462-10. 1939 Convention. Pullman Rates
    - General, 1939-1940 (Box 601b, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 462-11. 1939 Convention. Transportation for Delegates
    - General, 1939 (Box 601b, Folder 6)
- Series XCIII. WASHINGTON JOB PROTECTION AGREEMENT OF MAY 1936
  - Sub-Series 469-0. Washington Job Protection Agreement of May 1936. General
    - Report of Subcommittee of Enochs-Harrison Committee Regarding Southern Pacific Railway Company and Texas and New Orleans Railway Company Car Department Facilities at El Paso, Texas, 1940 (Box 602a, Folder 1)
      1940 May 1
    - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railway, 1939 (Box 602a, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings. Section 13 Committee, 1962 (Box 602a, Folder 3)
      1962 December, 11
    - Proceedings. Section 13 Committee, 1962 (Box 602a, Folder 4)
      1962 December, 12
    - Proceedings. Section 13 Committee, 1962 (Box 602a, Folder 5)
      1962 December, 13
    - Proceedings. Section 13 Committee, 1962 (Box 602a, Folder 6)
      1962 December, 14
    - Report. Section 13 Committee, 1942 (Box 602a, Folder 7)
      1942 October 23
    - Master File. Davis, W.M., 1936-1951 (Box 602a, Folder 8)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 602a, Folder 9)
    - 1939-1943 (Box 602a, Folder 10)
    - Car Inspection Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 602b, Folder 1)
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad. Payroll Data, 1937-1938 (Box 602b, Folder 2)
      April 16, 1937-April 15, 1938.
    - Enochs-Harrison Committee Regarding Southern Pacific Railway Company and Texas and New Orleans Railway Company Car Department Facilities at El Paso, Texas. Brief of Railway Employees' Department, American Federation of Labor, 1940 (Box 602b, Folder 3)
      1940 March 22
    - Excerpts from Minutes of Railway Labor Executives' Association Meetings, 1936-1938 (Box 602b, Folder 4)
    - Agreement, Supplements, Revisions, and Interpretations, 1939-1946 (Box 602b, Folder 5)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company; Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Company; Louisiana, Arkansas and Texas Railway Company, 1938-1940 (Box 602b, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railway and Norfolk and Southern Railway Company, 1939 (Box 602b, Folder 7)
    - St. Louis Municipal Bridge, 1938-1939 (Box 602b, Folder 8)
    - 1936-1938 (Box 602b, Folder 9)
    - 1936-1938 (Box 602b, Folder 10)
    - Section 13 Committee, 1941-1951 (Box 602b, Folder 11)
      1941-August 1951.
    - Section 13 Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 602b, Folder 12)
      January 15, 1958-November 12, 1959.
    - 1938-1950 (Box 602b, Folder 13)
    - Section 13 Committee. Transcript of Hearings, 1957 (Box 602b, Folder 14-18)
      September 17-20, 1957.
    - Court Decisions, 1953-1954 (Box 602b, Folder 19)
      December 1953-June 1954.
    - October 1952-November 1953 (Box 603a, Folder 1)
    - July 1951-September 1952 (Box 603a, Folder 2)
    - January 18, 1951-June 1951 (Box 603a, Folder 3)
    - February 1950-January 17, 1951 (Box 603a, Folder 4)
    - July 1949-Janaury 1950 (Box 603a, Folder 5)
    - November 1948-June 1949 (Box 603a, Folder 6)
    - February 1948-October 1948 (Box 603a, Folder 7)
    - July 1947-January 1948 (Box 603a, Folder 8)
    - February-June 1947 (Box 603a, Folder 9)
    - October 1946-January 1947 (Box 603a, Folder 10)
    - May-September 1946 (Box 603a, Folder 11)
    - January-April 1946 (Box 603a, Folder 12)
    - Questions and Answers, 1936-1945 (Box 604a, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 469-2. Washington Job Protection Agreement of May 1936. Roads Not Parties
    - Awards of Section 13 Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 604a, Folder 2)
      1960-October 1962.
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1936-1956 (Box 604a, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Region, 1936-1954 (Box 604a, Folder 4)
    - Eastern Region, 1939-1951 (Box 604a, Folder 5)
    - Eastern Region, 1936-1951 (Box 604a, Folder 6)
    - Southeastern Region, 1936-1954 (Box 604a, Folder 7)
    - Southeastern Region, 1939-1952 (Box 604a, Folder 8)
    - Southeastern Region, 1936-1950 (Box 604a, Folder 9)
    - Western Region, 1936-1957 (Box 604a, Folder 10)
    - Southeastern Region, 1936-1950 (Box 604b, Folder 1)
    - Western Region, 1936-1956 (Box 604b, Folder 2)
    - Western Region, 1936-1952 (Box 604b, Folder 3)
    - Western Region, 1936-1956 (Box 604b, Folder 4)
    - Western Region, 1936-1954 (Box 604b, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1936-1939 (Box 604b, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Fruit Express, 1939-1947 (Box 604b, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta, Georgia Joint Terminals, 1936-1942 (Box 604b, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Great Western Railway, 1936-1942 (Box 604b, Folder 9)
    - Buffalo Creek Railroad, 1936 (Box 604b, Folder 10)
    - Central Vermont Railroad, 1939 (Box 604b, Folder 11)
    - Duluth, Winnipeg and Pacific Railway Company, 1936-1937 (Box 604b, Folder 12)
    - Grand Trunk Railroad, 1936 (Box 604b, Folder 13)
    - Gulf, Mobile and Northern Railroad, 1939 (Box 604b, Folder 14)
    - Hannibal, Missouri Union Depot Company, 1936 (Box 604b, Folder 15)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway, 1939 (Box 604b, Folder 16)
    - Louisiana and Arkansas Railway; Louisiana, Arkansas and Texas Railway, 1939 (Box 604b, Folder 17)
    - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad. Case No. A-789, 1936-1941 (Box 604b, Folder 18)
    - Sacramento Northern Railway, 1940 (Box 604b, Folder 19)
    - Troy Union Railroad Company, 1940-1941 (Box 604b, Folder 20)
    - Southern Railway Company, 1936-1940 (Box 604b, Folder 21)
    - Union Depot, Columbus, Ohio, 1936 (Box 604b, Folder 22)